Hello friends, welcome to the SBI
Securities Morning Podcast.
Indian industrials finally broke its four-day losing streak
and ended higher, led by buying by auto
and financial stocks, which after two
days of selling by the FPIs finally turned net
buyers.  Similarly, these were net bearers
as was the case previously for the past week.
If we look at the US markets,
consumer prices shot cooling off.  So that was
a good sign.  But at the end of the day,
SAP still closed lower, mainly driven
by the fact that financial companies'
results were very mixed.
Asian markets also failed at the open.  And the
reason for this is that looking at the US inflation data,
hopes that fate will cut the interest
rates are decreasing.  Key data points to watch
for the day are for the UK CPI numbers
will be out.  For Europe trade balance data
will be out and for the US lot of data
will be out there such as the industrial
production the US producer price
index and the crude inventories along with
that the US inflation rate year on year is
2.7 and on month on month basis is 0.3 and
if we look at the earnings then today Tech
Mahindra ITC Hotels Anjal 1 TB corr Kalp
through LNT Technological Services among other
names will have their earnings report today.
If we look at yesterday's post market results,
ICICI LBD's results were good.
HDFC Life Insurance and JStile's
results were decent and HDB Financials'
results were weak.  If we look at the stocks and focus,
Biocon Biologic, an arm of Biocon, has expanded its
diabetes portfolio with FD approval of
Christine.  This is the first and only
interchangeable rapid acting insulin available
in the USA.  Zydus Life Sciences has
received final approval from the US FDA
for Celixib Capsules, a non-
steroidal anti-inflammatory drug.
Cupid has approved an investment in
GII Health Care Investments,
marking its first strategic entry
into the Middle East markets.  CFF
Fluid Control Signs an Agreement with the
Garden Reach Shipbuilders to Enhance Its
Naval and Marine Systems Portfolio.
MTL has
defaulted on bank loans and
interest payments to the tune of ₹8585 crore.  Lemon Tree has
opened a new 64-room hotel in Tamil Nadu.
Anupam Rasayans has allotted 39 lakh
shares at Rs 945.1 per
share upon conversion of ₹39 lakh
warrants.  And Himadri Speciality Chemicals has
approved the incorporation of a wholly
owned subsidiary in UAE which is known as
Alliance Worldwide LLC to expand its
overseas operations and if we
look at the block deals, Nipon India
Mutual Fund
bought 20 lakh shares in MS Financial Services which was up
around 0.11% at the ₹35 per share.
With this we end today's podcast.
Hope you stay tuned for tomorrow.
Investment in security is market are
subject to market risk.  Read all the
related documents carefully before
investing.